{"data":[{"question":"There are a school for young children in Elgol, but the older children have to travel into the town.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"doesn't","b":"that","c":"drinks","d":"be","answer":"1","explain":"- Doesn't-> don't","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"Sometimes it takes me about three hours finishing my round.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"oftenly","b":"have","c":"through","d":"badly","answer":"1","explain":"- Oftenly-> often","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"Stories are the goodest way of teaching moral lessons to young people.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"woman","b":"watching","c":"waiting","d":"to join","answer":"1","explain":"- Woman-> women","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"I talk about the Tower of London, and then of the lives of people in England today.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"dark","b":"reflects","c":"which","d":"many","answer":"4","explain":"- Many-> much","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"Sun Jingxiu, a 80-year-old retired teacher, is the oldest storyteller in the country.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"spent","b":"to find","c":"so that","d":"telling","answer":"4","explain":"- Telling-> to tell","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"Small children doesn't understand that hot water and hot drinks can be dangerous.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"something","b":"to eat","c":"were","d":"in","answer":"3","explain":"- Were-> was","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"More oftenly the children have fallen through a glass door or window and are badly hurt.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"In","b":"was","c":"until","d":"years","answer":"2","explain":"- Was-> were","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"Her dark dress reflects a view of life which is many less optimistic.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Most","b":"wears","c":"that","d":"from","answer":"2","explain":"- Wears-> wear","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"I spent an hour trying to find a phone so that I could ring you telling you I'd be a little late this morning.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"of","b":"build","c":"nineteenth","d":"are","answer":"2","explain":"- Build-> built","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"I wanted something fresh to eat while I were in Britain.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"were","b":"to persuade","c":"to drink","d":"with","answer":"4","explain":"- With-> of","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"}]}